## **Walter Greenwich**

## **Full Stack Developer**

+51 925761063 waltgreenwich.devsec@gmail.com Lima, Perú in/walter-greenwich-link/ github.com/WGreenwichChaca // /Portfolio

## **Profile Summary**

Full Stack developer with experience in JavaScript, Next.js, React, Node.js, PostgreSQL, MongoDB, Tailwind, Redux, Express and API Rest. My professional career includes participation in group and individual practices and projects, which has allowed me to acquire deep knowledge of Full Stack development. Additionally, I hold a Bachelor's degree in Genetics and Biotechnology. I am committed to continuous learning and constantly improving my skills. I am comfortable working in agile environments using methodologies such as SCRUM, and I have experience using tools such as GIT for version control.

## **Work Experience**

# ESPAÑOL CON E Full Stack Developer (internship)

Córdova, ARG 05/2024 - 05/2024

 Modified, edited and updated the pages of the new B2 level Spanish classes using Next.js and MongoDB, improving usability and user experience.

## **Other experiences:**

#### **DOENK PER**

#### **Administrative Assistant**

Chiclayo, PER 01/2023 - 11/2023

- Wrote and responded to emails to various clients.
- · Coordinate meetings and calls with assigned sales representatives.
- Generated a 15% increase in new clients in 6 months by intensifying sales and making strategic visits to clients to close deals.

#### **AHSECO PERU**

#### **Sales Executive**

Lima, PER *05/2019 - 10/2022* 

- Developed sales processes based on lead generation, marketing strategies, client meetings, and sales closures.
- Exceeded the company's defined sales quota target for monthly sales revenue, achieving over 20% growth in the sales department in just 6 months.

### **Technical Skills**

- Programming Languages: JavaScript.
- Tools and Frameworks: Next.js, React, Redux, Node.js, Express, Sequelize, Tailwind.
- Databases: PostgreSQL, MongoDB.
- Collaboration Tools: Git, Trello, Jira, Slack.
- · Agile Methodologies: SCRUM.

## **Languages**

• English: Intermediate

• Spanish: Native

## **Professional Education**

- Full Stack Developer. Henry Bootcamp. 800 hours in theoretical and practical course. 2023-2024
- Bachelor's Degree in Genetics and Biotechnology. Universidad Nacional Mayor de San Marcos. 2011-2016

## **Projects**

**1. Frontend-React: <WeatherApp>.** <u>Demo</u> - <u>Repository</u> May.2024

May. 2024 -

**Goals:** Develop and design a web app using React including React Hooks for state management, Tailwind CSS for responsive design and consumption of the OpenWeatherMap API to obtain weather data.

**2. Full Stack: <Event\_App>.** Repository Apr. 2024

Mar. 2024 –

**Goals:** Develop and Design a Single Page Application that integrates a payment gateway with Stripe and Google authentication.

**3. Full Stack: <Countries\_App>.** Demo - Repository Feb. 2024

Jan. 2024 -

**Goals:** Develop and design a single-page application, including search, filtering, sorting of countries, and creation of tourist activities.

## **Complementary Education**

- Basic aspects of user experience design. Google-Coursera. 2024
- Learning TypeScript. LinkedIn Learning. 2024
- Frontend Oracle Next Education. Alura Latam. 2023